Guide to the UH Statistics Records
University of Houston Libraries
UH Statistics Records
1947-1970
1969-069
University of Houston
16.00 Linear Feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
The UH Statistics Records contain various reports issued by the University. Some of the topics of these reports include Teacher Load Reports, New Students, Statistics, Coordinating Board Reports, and Grade Distribution Reports.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
University of Houston
Genre/Form of Material:
Reports
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research.
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Scope and Contents
The UH Statistics Records contain various reports issued by the University. Some of the topics of these reports include Teacher Load Reports, New Students, Statistics, Coordinating Board Reports, and Grade Distribution Reports.
The collection is arranged chronologically with the materials beginning in 1947 and ending in 1970.
Detailed List of Contents
- A Study of Administrative Management - Chapter VI: University Development Activities (Box 1, Folder 1)
- A Study of Administrative Management - Volume One (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A Study of Administrative Management - Volume Two (Box 1, Folder 3)
- University of Houston Teacher Load Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 4-7)
- Enrollment Analysis - Book 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- New Students - Book 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Student Roster ALPH, Fall 1954 through 2nd Summer 1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Grade Distribution, 2nd Summer 1954 (Binder 4)
- Statistics, Fall 1955 through 2nd Summer 1956 (Binder 5)
- Statistics, Fall 1956 through 2nd Summer 1957 (Binder 6)
- Statistics, Fall 1956 through 2nd Summer 1957 (Binder 7)
- JCA - Book 1 of 2, 1957 (Binder 8)
- JCA - Book 2 of 2, 1957 (Binder 9)
- Statistics, Fall 1957 through 2nd Summer 1958 (Binder 10)
- Statistics, Fall 1957 through 2nd Summer 1958 (Binder 11)
- Cresap, McCormick, and Paget Report, 1959 (Binder 12)
- Statistics, Fall 1958 through 2nd Summer 1959 (Binder 13)
- Statistics, Fall 1958 through 2nd Summer 1959 (Binder 14)
- Rank Masters - Campus and Downtown, Fall 1959 (Binder 15)
- Statistics, Fall 1959 through 2nd Summer 1960 (Binder 16)
- Statistics, Fall 1960 through 2nd Summer 1961 (Binder 17)
- Schedule Listing - Book 2 (Binder 18)
- Statistics, Fall 1961 through 2nd Summer 1962 (Binder 19)
- Statistics, Fall 1961 through 2nd Summer 1962 (Binder 20)
- Statistics, Fall 1962 through 2nd Summer 1963 (Binder 21)
- Statistics, Fall 1962 through 2nd Summer 1963 (Binder 22)
- Statistics, Fall 1963 through 2nd Summer 1964 (Binder 23)
- Statistics, Fall 1964 through 2nd Summer 1965 (Binder 24)
- Statistics, Fall 1965 (Binder 25)
- Coordinating Board Reports, Spring 1965 through 2nd Summer 1965 (Binder 26)
- Statistics, Spring 1966 (Binder 27)
- Statistical, 1st and 2nd Summer 1966 (Binder 28)
- Statistical, Fall 1966 (Binder 29)
- Coordinating Board Reports, Fall 1966 through 2nd Summer 1967 (Binder 30)
- Registrar's Statistical, Spring 1967 through 2nd Summer 1967 (Binder 31)
- Grade Distribution, Spring 1967, Fall 1967, Spring 1968 (Binder 32)
- Fall 1967 through 2nd Summer 1968 (Binder 33)
- Department Major Classification Report, Fall 1969 (Binder 34)
- Department Major Classification Report, Spring 1970 (Binder 35)